<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Movement on Being Human</title>
    <link>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/tags/movement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Movement on Being Human</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://noriparelius.netlify.app/tags/movement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An ode to human gait</title>
      <link>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/ode_to_gait/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/ode_to_gait/</guid>
      <description>There are probably several magical ingredients in the soup of humanity that make us who we are; like big brains, opposable thumbs and a tendency to cooperate. And among these, we can definitely list our gait too.&#xA;The way we humans walk is unique in the natural world. Moving around on two legs freed up those opposable thumbs for other purposes, allowed us to throw things, carry things and use tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I found out I had to move more and move better</title>
      <link>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/move-more-move-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/move-more-move-better/</guid>
      <description>Disconnected and dysfunctional I used to be a nerdy little bookworm as a kid and as a teenager. And honestly a bit of a couch potato. If I could sit in a comfy armchair with a book, I would sit in a comfy armchair with a book.&#xA;I also used to be a &amp;ldquo;good girl&amp;rdquo;. Doing what I was expected to do and following the rules both spoken and implied. So I would sit &amp;ldquo;properly&amp;rdquo;, never run around in the corridors and favour academic achievements over physical prowess.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movement moves the brain - why dancing is better than sudoku</title>
      <link>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/movement-moves-the-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/movement-moves-the-brain/</guid>
      <description>Can I drop my body off at the gym and pick it up when it&amp;rsquo;s done? As a teenager I used to always listen to music or audiobooks when I went for a run. I did it because running and exercise were a chore - a boring, annoying, but necessary chore. I didn&amp;rsquo;t do it for the fun of it. I just wanted to lose weight and get into shape (mostly so that I would be able to run away from the aliens if I found myself in an episode of Doctor Who).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
