<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food on Being Human</title>
    <link>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/tags/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food on Being Human</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://noriparelius.netlify.app/tags/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is the natural human diet?</title>
      <link>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/natural-human-diet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/natural-human-diet/</guid>
      <description>Humans are probably the only creatures in the world that are confused about what they should be eating.&#xA;Pandas eat bambus, koalas eucalyptys. Cows eat grasses and wolves eat meat. Most animals have a very limited menu. Yet humans are trying to eat &amp;ldquo;a varied diet&amp;rdquo;, to &amp;ldquo;eat the rainbow&amp;rdquo;. Something that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t make sense for most animals on Earth.&#xA;What are we meant to eat? What is the natural human diet?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We have a blind spot</title>
      <link>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/blind-spot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/blind-spot/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my name is Nori, and I am an addict. For the longest time, I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to admit it to myself. I thought I was in control. I thought I was &amp;ldquo;moderating&amp;rdquo;, whatever that might mean. But in truth I was moderating myself to a serving of my drug of choice dozens of times every day. Simply because I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t feel good without it. Simply because I wanted it. A lot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are our bodies trying to kill us?</title>
      <link>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/bodies-trying-kill-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/bodies-trying-kill-us/</guid>
      <description>I have recently finished reading Malcolm Kendrick&amp;rsquo;s books The Great Cholesterol Con and The Clot Thickens and it was a treat. It was insightful, captivating and so very funny, just dripping with dry, British humour. And with frustration. A LOT of frustration.&#xA;What causes heart disease? The cholesterol hypothesis He is on a mission to tell people that the cholesterol hypothesis of cardiovascular disease is wrong.&#xA;The cholesterol hypothesis:&#xA;The amount of saturated fat we eat increases the level of LDL (Low Density Lipoprotein) particles in the blood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I became a carnivore</title>
      <link>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/how-i-became-carnivore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/how-i-became-carnivore/</guid>
      <description>I don’t eat a “varied and balanced diet” anymore. I don’t do five a day. There is no rainbow on my plate. And no holy (whole) grains. Zero fibre, actually. On the other hand, I eat lots of saturated fat, cholesterol and salt.&#xA;I eat meat, eggs, fish, salt and water. And that&amp;rsquo;s pretty much it 99% of the time.&#xA;And believe it or not I have never felt better.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
