<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About me on Being Human</title>
    <link>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/tags/about-me/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About me on Being Human</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 18:39:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://noriparelius.netlify.app/tags/about-me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My 5 reasons for blogging</title>
      <link>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/my-reasons-for-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 18:39:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/my-reasons-for-blogging/</guid>
      <description>(The image above is AI generated, the rest is not.)&#xA;I believe this is my fifth(?!) attempt at blogging in the last 12 years. Some of those blogs were very short-lived, some survived for longer. None of the previous four are out there anymore. I had my reasons for starting each of the blogs, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t something I thought about much, not something that was clear in my mind. As I was starting yet another blog (this one), I decided to be a bit more mindful and conscious of what my goals actually are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I became a carnivore</title>
      <link>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/how-i-became-carnivore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/how-i-became-carnivore/</guid>
      <description>I don’t eat a “varied and balanced diet” anymore. I don’t do five a day. There is no rainbow on my plate. And no holy (whole) grains. Zero fibre, actually. On the other hand, I eat lots of saturated fat, cholesterol and salt.&#xA;I eat meat, eggs, fish, salt and water. And that&amp;rsquo;s pretty much it 99% of the time.&#xA;And believe it or not I have never felt better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I found out I had to move more and move better</title>
      <link>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/move-more-move-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noriparelius.netlify.app/post/move-more-move-better/</guid>
      <description>Disconnected and dysfunctional I used to be a nerdy little bookworm as a kid and as a teenager. And honestly a bit of a couch potato. If I could sit in a comfy armchair with a book, I would sit in a comfy armchair with a book.&#xA;I also used to be a &amp;ldquo;good girl&amp;rdquo;. Doing what I was expected to do and following the rules both spoken and implied. So I would sit &amp;ldquo;properly&amp;rdquo;, never run around in the corridors and favour academic achievements over physical prowess.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
